ADAM KIM

CYBER SECURITY PROFESSIONAL, CYSA+

Dependable IT professional with over 5 years in various areas of tech, seeking to tackle and resolve complex security challenges. Ascertained a well-rounded knowledge in network, cyber security, helpdesk, and programming to increase availability and productivity. Sharp client communication and leadership delivering outstanding outcomes to the stake holders. Interested in a position in your company where these skill sets can be applied and further developed as we grow together.

Contact

Akim456@gmail.com

AtomKim.com

**** 347-554-3119

in AdamKim456

Resv

Education

2021

Per Scholas, Bronx NY Cyber Security Analyst

2018

Per Scholas, Bronx NY Java Developer

2015

Queens College, Queens

B.A. Media Studies

Certifications

Aug. 2021

CySA+ Cyber Security Analyst

CompTIA

Aug. 2021 Cyber Security Essentials

Cisco Certificate

Aug. 2021

Networking Essentials

Cisco Certificate

Aug. 2021

Linux Essentials

Cisco/NDG Certificate

Aug. 2021 **Notary Public**

U.S. Department of State (#01KI6420786)

Employment

The Law Offices of Kim & Associates

Network Engineer / Cyber Security GRC

Queens, NY Jan. 2019 - Current

Development and maintenance of network infrastructure, prioritized network availability and security for all employees within the company. Produced and preserved network & security policies to protect sensitive company and client data. Pioneered and implemented updated quarterly training on acceptable use policy. Strengthened company security posture by securing backups, isolating servers, and segmenting subnets. Responded and mitigated accordingly to any external and internal threats. Built and hardened all new and older machines. Collaborated directly with the DFS to develop cyber security polices in accordance to 23 NYCRR Part 500(e). Published, tested, & documented thorough contingency plans for disaster recovery & business continuity.

NETWORK

- · Redesigned physical and logical design of network infrastructure
- Segmented 2 private internal NAS's and external cloud via VPN Proxy
- · Modeled and administered user access and group policies, subnetting, and static IPs
- · Centralized end points to monitor malware, unauthorized apps, and system updates
- Strengthened wireless access securely for employees and limited access to visitors

CYBER SECURITY

- Routine analysis of malicious files and rogue devices
- Approved BYOD and applications upon inspection and analysis
- Performed audits, documented devices, SN/MAC addresses, and versions
- Orchestrated & instructed acceptable use policy and security practice trainings
- Authored a 23 CRR-NY-500(e) cyber security policy to completion for the business, approved by the Department of Financial Services

HELP DESK

- Assembled 25+ desktop PCs, troubleshooting, and responsible for equipment budgeting
- Converted 50+ office & home PCs overnight for remote, day 1 of the pandemic shutdown
- Imaged/clone hardened copies to reduce redeployment times of compromised machines
- Streamlined configurations for 20+ VoIP/analog phones, 5 printers, CCTV, and peripherals
- Developed automated scripts for employees and increased productivity and office morale
- Designed and deployed telepresence systems for 5 conference rooms for court proceedings due to the shift of the pandemic

ADAM KIM

CYBER SECURITY PROFESSIONAL, CYSA+

Skills

CYBER SECURITY

Packet Capture Analysis SIEM Tools, IDS / IPS Nmap / Zenmap

WAP Security

Virtualization

Hashing & Encryption

Hardening

Data Backup & Recovery

Secure Destruction

Policies & Compliance

NETWORK

Network Design
Network Administration
NAS & Cloud
Routers / Switches / Hubs
DHCP / Static / Subnetting
Port Forwarding
End Point / VoIP / CCTV

SOFTWARE

Windows / MAC / Linux

VMware

Wireshark

Packet Tracer

Nessus

Maltego

Itarian & Comodo

OBS / NDI / SRT / NGINX

HARDWARE

Building PCs

Routers & Switches

SOHO / Dell Sonic Wall

A/V Telepresence

Device Audit

Imaging / Cloning

PROGRAMMING

Java, SQL HTML5, CSS BATCH / DOS Auto Hot Key

AGILE / SDLC / SCRUM

Expert Googler

Employment

HSBC IT/AV Specialist Tri-state Oct. 2017 - June 2018

Team lead on multiple A/V projects for HSBC NYC Headquarters and neighboring branches across the tri-state. Accountable for A/V engineering for international conferences of up to 50 participants at one time, room surveys for Cisco telepresence system integrations, logistics, deploying, configuring, and decommissioning of systems.

- •Facilitated multiple ongoing projects simultaneously from start to completion
- •Coordinated with other departments such as IT to ensure deliverables were met
- •Projects were completed ahead of schedule while working safely and efficiently
- •Responsible for training, delegating assignments, and assessing quality of work
- Monitored broadcasts to deliver high quality, smooth, and efficient teleconferences
 Expert in surveying rooms for telepresence system installations and planning
- •Provided white glove customer service and communicated effectively with clients including system training and designing quick reference guides (QRG)

Law Office of Kwangsoo Kim

Queens, NY Jan. 2015 - Mar. 2017

Personal Injury Protection (PIP) Admin

Expert in NY & NJ PIP / No-Fault procedures. Responsible for over 450 cases in various stages of litigation on the Supreme and Civil Court calendar in all 5 boroughs. Maintained persistent client relations, office administration, legal support for IME, EBT, 50H, and

- •No-Fault claims were set up and ensured all No-Fault documents were delivered
- •Assisted clients with lost wages, worker's comp, social security disability claims
- •Maintained all client medical bills and liens to avoid them from going into collections
- •Disputed and negotiated all medical bills, liens, and collections
- •Prepared documents for arbitration, NF arbitration, and medical summaries
- •Worked in liaison with all departments to ensure our clients had the best outcome at trial
- •Adhered to the rules and regulations of HIPAA compliance

Volunteering / Home Labs / Online Labs

VOLUNTEERING

discovery/response.

- •Cybersecurity consultant for Cascade Bicycle Club, providing pro bono assistance to conduct risk and vulnerability assessments, review the organization's policies, make recommendations, and implement best practices
- •Founder of CyberSeidon.com, offering free security advice/services for smaller businesses

HOME LAB

- •Nessus, Maltego, and Wireshark
- •VMware Hyper Visor 2 Ubuntu, Kali, 2x Win10, and Opnsense Firewall

ONLINE LAB

- TryHackMe (Profile)
- PicoCTF